Now what I want to do is,
现在 我们的任务是
I want to make each day that we filled out clickable.
让填充的每一天都可点击
So, whenever I click on a day that looks like this,
每当我们点击这样的日期时
we get a nice little right to left transition.
能够出现从左到右的过渡效果
We dig higher into the route stack.
进一步访问路径堆栈
And then, we see some of the same statistics,
我们看到一些相同的统计信息
and we also see a reset button,
并且看到一个重置按钮
to be able to reset that specific day.
从而能够重置这一天
So there's a few things we need to do to do that.
因此 我们需要完成几项任务
First, let's go ahead and create a new file here,
首先 在这里新建一个文件
and we will call it EntryDetail.
称之为 EntryDetail
We're going to import React as well as
从 react-native 导入 React
the few other components that we typically use from react-native.
以及其他经常使用的组件
So we're just going to return a view with some text in it that says EntryDetail,
返回一个 View 其中具有文本“Entry Detail”
and then we need to make sure that we export this.
然后确保导出这个组件
All right, so now that we have this component,
我们已经创建好这个组件
inside of our app.js file,
现在转到 App.js 文件
the first thing we need to do is go ahead and import it.
首先导入该组件
And this is going to come from our components folder.
来自于 components 文件夹
And then now you'll notice that we currently are rendering this tabs component.
我们目前正在渲染这个 Tabs 组件
But because we are doing a different type of navigation now,
但是我们要实现的是另一种导航
instead of having tabs we're kind of going into the route hierarchy as I've mentioned.
我们不再用到标签页 正如之前提到的 我们要访问路径层级结构
We actually need a StackNavigator.
我们实际上需要 StackNavigator
And so from react-navigation,
因此 从 react-navigation 中
we can get the StackNavigator function.
导入 StackNavigator 函数
So now what we can do,
转到这里
is we come in here and just like we did with our tab navigator.
就像 TabNavigator 那样
Let's make a new variable we'll call it MainNavigator.
我们新建一个变量 叫做 MainNavigator
We'll set that equal to the invocation of StackNavigator and
设为等于 StackNavigator 的调用结果
the properties that are on this object are going to be our new routes.
该对象上的属性将为新的路径
So we will see home,
输入 Home
and what this is going to be,
它将渲染
it's going to render the tab's component.
Tabs 组件
So what we're doing here is we are rendering this component right here,
我们在渲染这个组件
which is then rendering those tabs,
然后选择这些标签页
and you'll see why that is important here in a second.
稍后你就会看到为何这么做很重要
And then, what we want to do is we have EntryDetail.
然后输入 EntryDetail
Screen is going to be that EntryDetail component that we just barely made.
Screen 将为我们刚刚创建的这个 EntryDetail 组件
And then, we will give it some navigation options real quick.
然后快速设置一些导航选项
We will say headerTintColor.
将 headerTintColor 设为 white
Let's go ahead and make that white and then we will say headersStyle,
将 headersStyle 的
I'll give this a background color of purple.
backgroundColor 设为 purple
All right, so now instead of rendering tabs right here,
这里 我们不再渲染 Tabs
what we actually want to render is our MainNavigator.
而是渲染 MainNavigator
So now let's check that everything is working fine.
看看一切是否正常
It looks like it is.
看起来正常
And you'll notice here that if I click on this, nothing is happening,
如果点击这个 什么也没发生
because if you remember inside of,
因为...如果你还记得的话
I believe it was history.js.
我记得是在 History.js 中
When we render that metric card we are wrapping it in this touchable opacity component,
当我们渲染该指标卡片时 我们将其封装在了这个 TouchableOpacity 组件中
but all we're doing is we're constantly logging pressed.
但是我们的做法是不断输出“Pressed!”
What we want to do here because react-navigation is
因为现在 react-navigation 已经在控制我们的应用层次结构
now controlling our router and it's rendering this history component.
并且在渲染这个 History 组件
What we now have access to,
现在我们可以访问的是
is this.props.navigation.navigate as a function.
函数 this.props.navigation.navigate
So this is going to take us to a new screen.
这样将会转到新的屏幕
The first argument we pass it is going to be the screen that we're going to use,
传入的第一个参数将是我们要使用的屏幕
because we want to go to the EntryDetail screen.
因为我们要转到 EntryDetail 屏幕
And what's nice is we can also pass along information.
我们还可以传递一些信息
So we want to say, hey this screen that we want
我们要在此屏幕上显示的是
more details on are these specific entry that we want more details on,
我们想显示更多详情的具体条目
is this entry right here,
也就是这个条目
which is the key that we're getting from the third argument passed to render item.
它是一个 key 即传递给 renderItem 的第三个参数
So now, what's going to happen is,
现在
if this is working correctly,
如果一切正常的话
what we should see when I click on this,
当我点击这个时
we get taken to this new EntryDetail screen.
应该能转到这个新的 EntryDetail 屏幕
You'll notice that, the header is purple because that's what we specified right here.
你会发现 标题是紫色 因为我们在这里这么设置了
And the tint color is white which is that arrow right here.
着色是白色 也就是这个箭头
So now, what we want to do instead of just logging EntryDetail,
现在 我不再希望输出 Entry Detail
I actually want to go ahead and show as well
而是显示具体的 ID
the specific ID or the specific entry ID that we're passing along.
即传递的具体条目 ID
So, the way we can do that,
实现方式是…
this is kind of long but we can get it off of this.props.navigation.state.params.enrtyId.
有点长 输入 this.props.navigation.state.params.entryId
So now see how this looks,
看看应用显示效果
when we navigate to a specific screen.
当我们转到特定的屏幕时
You'll now notice we get EntryDetail but we also get
出现了 Entry Detail
the specific key of the data that we need
并且出现了要从 react store 中获取
to grab from our react store to show right here.
并显示在这里的数据的具体键